# Pseudo Wang. Jarvis Consulting

My name is Pseudo Wang. I graduated from York University in October 2022 with a degree in Computer Science. In the university, I learned a lot of fundamental knowledge about OOP principles, design patterns, web structures, operating system principles, and databases. Before entering the university, I worked in a startup company called Emerge Labs doing front-end related projects for different customers. In this company, I worked with designers and analyzed the client's needs to achieve the desired results. And this is the place I have gained valuable insight into how a successful company operates. After getting into university, I worked as a contracted data structure lecturer at an off-campus tutoring institution. I have helped many students achieve topping 10% grades in the Java Data Structures and Algorithms course. In this process, I significantly improved my explanatory skills to better help students understand the content. I have finished multiple paid website works independently in my career path. Those projects involve different back-end technologies (Node.js/Flask/Nginx) and different cloud services (AWS/Azure/Oracle Cloud). You can find a self-build combined website framework on my GitHub using Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB, also practice projects of Angular and React starting a couple of years ago. Based on interest, I have also made an internet-based Android App using Android Studio in my spare time. Recently, I used GitHub Pages and GitHub Actions to build an auto-deployed web page involving CI/CD workflows. I am a self-starter and motivated team player with the ability to accomplish tasks independently. Through my work experience and other professional activities. I have strengthened my interpersonal and presentation skills. Also, with reliable communication ability and strong coding skills, I'm always the team leader in school projects and company projects.

#### Skills

Proficient: Git, Java, Nginx, NodeJS, SQL/NoSQL, Linux/Bash, Agile/Scrum

Competent: React, Angular, Vue/Vite, ExpressJS, C Language, AWS/Azure/OracleCloud

Familiar: Flask, Python, Kotlin, Django, Android

#### **Jarvis Projects**

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis\_data\_eng\_PseudoWang

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: This project is used to recording the hardware specifications in real-time and storing data into an RDBMS.

#### Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

- Twitter App
- JDBC App
- Grep App

## **Highlighted Projects**

Combined Website Framework [GitHub]: A Full-Stack project can be deployed on the cloud server such as AWS. The back-end server uses Node.js, and the database uses MongoDB. The front-end uses Express.js Framework with Webpack, applied Google Material Design, contains User Verification System, Injection Protection, etc.

GUI Othello Game [GitHub]: A GUI Othello Game that can be played as Player vs. Player or Player vs. Machine locally. Using JavaFX as GUI framework. Applied the MVC model with several design patterns. Designed two different machine playing strategies.

Command-Line Chatroom [GitHub]: An Internet-Based Command-Line Chatroom, build by C Language and involving underlying network transmission. The project contains custom socket, server side, and client side.

#### **Professional Experiences**

Web Developer, Emerge Labs (2016-2017): Collaborate with designers to analyze client needs and create innovative interactive websites, one of them is: http://gongdaixie.com

Computer Science Lecturer, Future Up Inc (2019-2020): Reinforce knowledge of Java data structures taught at York University and help students achieve top 10% in their class.

# Education

York University (2018-2022), Bachelor of Sciences, Computer Science

### Miscellaneous

- Enterprise Design Thinking Certificates by IBM (2022)
  Competitive Algorithm Coding
- Video Editing